<xml>
    <brief>Get the list of all public OKAPI installations</brief>
    <issue-id>39</issue-id>
    <desc>
        Get the list of all public OKAPI installations. Keep in mind that
        OKAPI installations might differ slightly. If you plan on using
        multiple OKAPI installations in your application (which is a very
        good thing!) you should test it against the one with the <b>lowest</b>
        OKAPI version number.
    </desc>
    <common-format-params/>
    <returns>
        <p>A dictionary of the following structure:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <b>site_name</b> - universal name for this site (should be fine
                for all languages),
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>site_url</b> - URL of the Opencaching site which is running
                the OKAPI installation (usually this looks like
                "http://www.opencaching.<i>xx</i>/", where <b>xx</b> is a top
                level domain of a country). If you prefer either http or https
                access, evaluate <b>https</b> to find out if the desired
                scheme is available, and eventually replace the scheme in the
                <b>site_url</b> string.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>okapi_base_url</b> - URL of the OKAPI installation (usually this is
                <b>site_url</b> with "okapi/" appended, but you should not assume
                that); this value is to be used as a prefix when constructing service
                method URLs. If you prefer either http oder https access, evaluate
                <b>https</b> to find out if the desired scheme is available, and
                eventually replace the scheme in the <b>okapi_base_url</b> string.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>https</b> - https support of the Opencaching site and the OKAPI
                installation; one of the following:
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <b>unavailable</b> - https will not work (properly) or will be redirected to http,
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>availaible</b> - http and https will both work,
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>recommended</b> - http and https will both work, but http is
                        deprecated; if your application allows it, use https,
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>enforced</b> - http will be redirected to https.
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ul>
    </returns>
</xml>